<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Almeria Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="beaches">Beaches</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="entertainment">Enter\ntainment</string>
    <string name="monuments">Monu\nments</string>


    <string name="entertainment_1">La Bambalina Restaurant</string>
    <string name="entertainment_1_location">Calle Padre Alfonso Torres, 14</string>

    <string name="entertainment_2">Cafe Cyrano</string>
    <string name="entertainment_2_location">Calle Mendez Nuñez, 19</string>

    <string name="entertainment_3">Karting Garrucha</string>
    <string name="entertainment_3_location">Aptdo. Correos 498 (Garrucha)</string>

    <string name="entertainment_4">Share Lock Scape Room</string>
    <string name="entertainment_4_location">Calle Minas de Gador, 6</string>

    <string name="entertainment_5">Monumental Cinema</string>
    <string name="entertainment_5_location">Centro Comercial Mediterraneo, Avda. del Mediterraneo s/n</string>

    <string name="entertainment_6">Cabo de Gata Kayak</string>
    <string name="entertainment_6_location">Calle Carr. Antigua del Faro, 57 (Cabo de Gata)</string>

    <string name="entertainment_7">Plaza de Toros</string>
    <string name="entertainment_7_location">Circunvalación Plaza de Toros, 04008</string>

    <string name="entertainment_8">Castor Park Roquetas</string>
    <string name="entertainment_8_location">Avenida Las Gaviotas (Roquetas de Mar)</string>

    <string name="entertainment_9">Ozone Bowling</string>
    <string name="entertainment_9_location">Paseo del Mediterraneo, 233 (Mojácar)</string>

    <string name="entertainment_10">Micro Theatre Almeria</string>
    <string name="entertainment_10_location">Calle Conde Ofalia, 10</string>

    <string name="entertainment_11">Paintball Supervivientes</string>
    <string name="entertainment_11_location">Polígono 16, Parcela 19 (Gergal)</string>


    <string name="beaches_1">Playa de Monsul</string>
    <string name="beaches_1_location">Parque Natural Cabo de Gata-Nijar (San Jose)</string>

    <string name="beaches_2">Playa de los Genoveses</string>
    <string name="beaches_2_location">Parque Natural Cabo de Gata-Nijar (San Jose)</string>

    <string name="beaches_3">Playa de Las Negras</string>
    <string name="beaches_3_location">Las Negras, 04116, Almeria</string>

    <string name="beaches_4">Playa de los Muertos</string>
    <string name="beaches_4_location">Carboneras, Almeria</string>

    <string name="beaches_5">Cala de Enmedio</string>
    <string name="beaches_5_location">Agua Amarga, Almeria</string>

    <string name="beaches_6">Playa de Aguadulce</string>
    <string name="beaches_6_location">Aguadulce, Roquetas de Mar, Almeria</string>

    <string name="beaches_7">Playa de los Escullos</string>
    <string name="beaches_7_location">Los Escullos, Nijar, Almeria</string>

    <string name="beaches_8">Playa de El Playazo</string>
    <string name="beaches_8_location">Rodalquilar, Nijar, Almeria</string>

    <string name="beaches_9">Playa de Las Salinas</string>
    <string name="beaches_9_location">Cabo de Gata, Almeria</string>


    <string name="monuments_1">Alcazaba</string>
    <string name="monuments_1_location">Calle Almanzor, s/n</string>

    <string name="monuments_2">Catedral de Almeria</string>
    <string name="monuments_2_location">Plaza de la Catedral, 8</string>

    <string name="monuments_3">Refugios</string>
    <string name="monuments_3_location">Plaza Manuel Perez Garcia, 1</string>

    <string name="monuments_4">Museo de Almeria</string>
    <string name="monuments_4_location">Ctra. de Ronda, 91</string>

    <string name="monuments_5">Museo de la Guitarra</string>
    <string name="monuments_5_location">Ronda del Beato Diego Ventaja, s/n</string>

    <string name="monuments_6">Families Park</string>
    <string name="monuments_6_location">Av. del Mediterraneo, 71</string>

    <string name="monuments_7">Arabic Aljibes</string>
    <string name="monuments_7_location">Calle Tenor Iribarne, 12</string>

    <string name="monuments_8">Museum of Art "Doña Pakyta"</string>
    <string name="monuments_8_location">Plaza de Emilio Perez, 2</string>

    <string name="monuments_9">Town Hall Square</string>
    <string name="monuments_9_location">Plaza de la Constitucion, s/n</string>

    <string name="flag">Flag of Almeria</string>
    <string name="cable">Cable Ingles, at night</string>
    <string name="mariposas">House of the Butterflies</string>
    <string name="harbour">Harbour of Almeria</string>

    <string name="introduction">Introduction</string>
    <string name="short_description">Almeria is a city in Andalusia, Spain, situated in the southeast of Spain on the Mediterranean Sea.
        It is the capital of the province of the same name. It was Abd-ar-Rahman III who founded the Alcazaba (the Citadel),
        which gave this city its name: Al-Mari\'yah. In the 10th and 11th centuries, it formed part of the Caliphate of Cordoba,
        and grew wealthy on trade and the textile industry, especially silk. It suffered many sieges and fell under Christian domination in 1489.
        In 1522, Almeria was devastated by an earthquake and rebuilding and recovery didn\'t really get underway until the 19th century.
        During the Spanish Civil War, the city was shelled by the German Navy, and fell to Franco in 1939. It has since rebuilt its
        economy around vegetable production, with 100,000 acres of greenhouses, supplying much of Europe</string>

    <string name="main_sights">Main sights</string>
    <string name="main_sights_description">\t\t•\t\tThe Alcazaba, a medieval fortress that was begun in the 10th century but destroyed by an
        earthquake in 1522. It includes a triple line of walls, a majestic keep and large gardens. It commands a city quarter with buildings
        dressed in pastel colors, of Muslim-age aspect.\n
        \t\t•\t\tAlmeria air raid shelters, underground galleries for civilian protection during the Spanish Civil War, nowadays, the longest in
        Europe open for tourists.\n
        \t\t•\t\tThe Cathedral has a fortress-like appearance due to its towers, merlons and protected paths, created to defend it from Mediterranean
        pirates. Originally designated as a mosque, it was later converted into a Christian church, before being destroyed in the 1522
        earthquake. In the 16th century it was rebuilt in the Renaissance style, whilst keeping some of its defensive features.\n
        \t\t•\t\tRenaissance church of Santiago, built in 1533, with tower and portal decorated with reliefs.\n
        \t\t•\t\tChanca, a group of houses carved into rocks.\n
        \t\t•\t\tCastle of San Cristobal, now in ruins. It is connected to the Alcazaba by a line of walls.\n
        \t\t•\t\tMuseum of Almeria. Includes findings from Prehistoric, Iberic, Roman, Greek ages and Muslim objects, mostly from the Alcazaba.\n
        \t\t•\t\tPaseo de Coches, a modern seaside promenade with gardens and palms</string>

    <string name="people">People and culture</string>
    <string name="people_description">Famous natives of Almeria include Nicolas Salmeron y Alonso, who in 1873 was the third president of the First
        Spanish Republic, as well as several musicians, including the composer Jose Padilla Sanchez, whose music was declared of universal
        interest by Unesco in 1989, the popular folk singer Manolo Escobar, renowned Flamenco guitar player Tomatito and Grammy Award winner
        David Bisbal; the champion motorcyclist Antonio Maeso moved to Almeria as a child.</string>

    <string name="sports">Sports</string>
    <string name="sports_description">Almeria hosted the Mediterranean Games in 2005. The city has 2 football teams: UD Almeria, which plays in the Spanish
        Segunda Division following relegation from La Liga in 2013 and CP Almeria, in regional division.</string>

    <string name="geography">Geography</string>
    <string name="geography_description">Due to its arid landscape, numerous spaghetti westerns were filmed in Almeria. According to Christopher Frayling,
        the author of Once Upon a Time in Italy: The Films of Sergio Leone, some of the sets are still there. These sets are located in the
        desert of Tabernas. The town and region were also used by David Lean in Lawrence of Arabia (1962), John Milius in The Wind and the
        Lion (1975) and others.\n
        One of Almeria\'s most famous natural spots is the Cabo de Gata-Nijar Natural Park. This park is of volcanic
        origin, and is the largest and most ecologically significant marine-terrestrial space in the European Western Mediterranean Sea.
        With one of the most beautiful and ecologically rich coasts of the western Mediterranean and an area of 380 square kilometres it is
        one of Spain\'s natural jewels. The Cabo de Gata-Nijar Natural Park runs through the municipal areas of Nijar, Almerimar and Carboneras.
        Its villages, previously dedicated to fishing, have become tourism spots for those interested in nature. One of the greatest attractions
        of the Cabo de Gata-Nijar Natural Park is its beaches.</string>

    <string name="climate">Climate</string>
    <string name="climate_description">With a yearly rain amount of just 200mm, Almeria city is the driest city in Europe and one of the driest on both
        shores of the Mediterranean coast. According to the Köppen climate classification, it is on the border between a hot semi-arid climate
        (BSh) and a true hot desert climate (BWh). The latter climate is present in nearby areas of Almeria province (such as the Cabo de
        Gata-Níjar Natural Park, the Almanzora River valley and Tabernas Desert), the only region in Europe to have this climate. With an
        average annual temperature above 19 °C it also qualifies as the 2nd warmest city in continental Europe, after Seville, also in
        Andalusia, Spain. The dry season (although there is no real wet season) occurs during the hottest months, as in the Mediterranean
        climate. This climatic region spreads along the coastline around Almeria, from approximately Almerimar to the west, to Murcia province
        in the north-east.\n </string>

    <string name="climate_description_2">
        Almeria also experiences the warmest winters of any city on the European continent with a population over 100,000,
        and hot and dry summers with no precipitation between June and September. Almeria enjoys about 3000 hours of sunshine annually with
        over 320 sunny days a year on average (6 hours of sunshine in January and 12 in July). The city has an average of only 26 days with
        precipitation annually.\n
        Almeria is unique, for a city in Continental Europe, for not having any registered temperature under the freezing mark in its recorded
        weather history. The coldest temperature recorded was 0.2 °C (32.4 °F) on 9 February 1935. The city of Almeria has a very warm climate
        for its latitude, as it has a very similar climate to Alexandria, in Egypt, which is located further south at 31ºN latitude.\nDuring
        the winter, daily maximum temperatures tend to stay around 18 °C (64 °F). At night, the temperature very rarely drops below
        8 °C (46 °F). Precipitation even during the wettest months is rare, this falls in short showers or thunderstorms. Inland areas of the
        Almería province have reached 50 °C (122 °F) in summer.\nDuring the warmest months - July and August, the sky is clear and sunny and
        no rainfall occurs. The typical daily temperatures are around 33 °C (91 °F) during the heat of the day. This is often influenced by
        the Levant wind, a hot dry easterly wind that blows from the interior desert that makes temperatures soar to 38 °C (100 °F) or higher.
        These can also carry dust or sand. The minimum temperatures stay around 24 °C (75 °F) during July and August. Heatwaves in Almería are
        quite common; Almería reached up to 43 °C (109 °F) in August 2011.\n </string>
</resources>
